

Nosheen Gulzar

Human Resource Manager

I have varied experience in office Administration, Financial Controls and Management of an office independently. I can manage projects from the grass-root level till their completion on all its fields and manifestations. Can solve all computer related matters with perfection in management of office & projects.

gulzar.noshi@hotmail.com

03228504983

Rawalpindi, Pakistan

25 October, 1988

WORK EXPERIENCE

Event Manager

Confidential

2018 - Present

- Writing event proposals and contracts.
- Briefing and debriefing your event teams.
- Organize employees activities events.

Human Resource Manager

Reach First Inc.

08/2018 - Present.

Islamabad, Pakistan

- Human Resource Planning and Hiring Candidates.
- Training and Development.
- Design Workplace policies and Monitor Performance and Payroll and Appraisals.
- Stress Management and Social Security.

Human Resource/Project Lead ACE Money Transfer (Citizen Society)

09/2016 - 09/2018.

Kharian, Pakistan

- Leading project planning sessions, Coordinating staff and internal Resources.
- Managing project progress and adapt work as required.
- Designing and Signing-off on contracts.

Principal

Lahore Grammar School

08/2015 - 08/2016,

Kharian, Pakistan

- Managing various activities of the firm's onging projects.
- Coordinating with on-field staff and clients and Analysis of ongoing and future projects.
- Developing and managing relationships with potential clients.

Branch Head

Roots International School

07/2012 - 08/2015.

Kharian, Pakistan

- Responsible for general administration, facility management, asset management, procurement, organisational discipline, maintenance issues.
- Leading & performing operational planning functions for Roots Intl.
- Managing all the administrative activities at the Head Office & nationwide campuses.

Cordinator

Roots International School

06/2010 - 07/2012,

Kharian, Pakistan

SKILLS



HONOR AWARDS

Honoured to receive gold Medal.

Roots International School.

One bronze Medal As Principal and Branch Head.

Roots International School

EDUCATION

Bsc Maths & Economics Govt College Kharian Cantt.

Kharian, Pakistan

INTERESTS



LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Urdu

Full Professional Proficie